Kotlin-backend developer, Ivanchuk Ivan

(+7) 988-061-84-72 | l3r8y@duck.com | t.me.l3r8y | blog | github.com/l3r8yJ | linkedin

About

I have my own open source projects, one of them is a Ruby library. It has reached **9k+ downloads**. You can find it and other projects or contributions in my <u>GitHub account</u>. Also I'm contributing in different open source projects. I am highly interested in the development of R&D and OSS, have experience in conducting research and publishing scientific papers, also have experience in developing programming language, maven plugins, static analysis and quality control tools. I have experience in teaching students in the discipline *Theory of Formal Languages*. Also, member of jury KaiCode OSS festival.

Experience

Samokat.tech | Kotlin Backend Developer | 23.10.2023 - present.

• Working on the clients tickets system. Developed a few OSS products during the working in project. Kotlin, Spring Boot, Spring Security, Spring Cloud, Gradle, Apache Kafka, RabbitMQ, PostgreSQL, Liquibase, Jooq

VTB | Java Team Lead | 30.08.2023 - 23.10.2023.

• Integration of banking systems. Work on CRM for the banking segment. Managing a team of 8 people. Java 11, Spring Boot, Spring Data, Spring Security, Spring Cloud, Spring WebFlux, Maven, Apache Kafka, RabbitMQ, PostgreSQL, Liquibase

VTB | Java Developer | 03.04.2023 - 30.08.2023.

• Integration of banking systems. Work on CRM for the banking segment.

Java 11, Spring Boot, Spring Data, Spring Security, Spring Cloud, Spring WebFlux, Maven, Apache Kafka, RabbitMQ, PostgreSQL, Liquibase

Open Source | Java developer | 24.06.2022 - present.

• R&D development. Worked on code quality control tools, eolang programming language, maven plugins Java, Maven, XSL, Docker, Unit Testing, Integration Testing, Rust, Ruby, EO, LATEX

INTERVOLGA | 19.04.2022 - 04.08.2022

• B2B development. Worked on integration of 1c-bitrix PHP, 1c-bitrix framework, SQL

Freelance | Java developer | May 2021 - April 2022

• Development of telegram bots for trading cryptocurrency platform Java, TelegramBots, Spring, SpringBoot, SpringData, Docker

Skills

- Java, Kotlin | Spring Boot, Spring Data, Spring Security, Spring Cloud, Spring WebFlux, Maven, Gradle, Liquibase
- RDBMS | PostgreSQL
- CI/CD | Openshift, K8s, TeamCity, Docker, GitHub Actions, rultor, 0pdd
- VCS | Git, GitHub, GitLab, Bitbucket
- Other | Ruby, Rust

Education

Volgograd State Technical University |

Bachelor, Engineering and Economics, Software engineering

2020 - 2024

Courses and etc.

Completely self-taught by reading books and practicing a lot.

I have a blog about software, perhaps it will be of interest to you.